<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
<messageboard>

<MESSAGE>
<identifier>(11 july 2009, 08.57)</identifier>
<author email='chang22609@yahoo.com'>Jane and Ed Chang</author>
<text>Congratulations! You guys spin a nice web! But I am still trying to win a little money from your mom!</text>
</MESSAGE>

<MESSAGE>
<identifier>(07 july 2009, 18.32)</identifier>
<author email='tia_liu@roadrunner.com'>Tia and Tyus</author>
<text>Congratulations Emily and Isaac! We are looking forward to seeing you get married this Saturday. Wow, so soon! (only 4 more days!!) &gt;_</text>
</MESSAGE>

<MESSAGE>
<identifier>(04 may 2009, 00.24)</identifier>
<author email='hsuanwenchang@gmail.com'>nancy and alex </author>
<text>hey,IsaacCongrats!!! you still remember us? Joe Lin's friends from UCR, we went to your bible study group when we went up to NorCal last spring.  We had a really good time with you guys!  Does Joe Lin even know you are getting married in July?? i should go tell him!again, congrats!</text>
</MESSAGE>

<MESSAGE>
<identifier>(30 april 2009, 22.47)</identifier>
<author email='jiazou@eecs.berkeley.edu'>Jia Zou</author>
<text>dude nice song haha! congrats!</text>
</MESSAGE>

<MESSAGE>
<identifier>(22 march 2009, 01.45)</identifier>
<author email='bryan@bryanjong.com'>Bryan</author>
<text>Congratulations!</text>
</MESSAGE>

<MESSAGE>
<identifier>(27 february 2009, 00.22)</identifier>
<author email='cheungster@yahoo.com'>Emily</author>
<text>Hey! Thank you all for commenting!!! I miss SB, 5th floor, AACF, and all the rest. =) It always makes me happy to think about those 4 years.</text>
</MESSAGE>

<MESSAGE>
<identifier>(24 february 2009, 21.38)</identifier>
<author email='jenniferguan@gmail.com'>Jen ^_^</author>
<text>you guys are so cute!! and nice job with the website, isaac!! i love it...so creative and easy to use. hi emily! =)</text>
</MESSAGE>

<MESSAGE>
<identifier>(23 february 2009, 15.44)</identifier>
<author email='leighannteh@gmail.com'>Leigh Ann</author>
<text>WOO WOO WOO!!!! WHAT A GOOD-LOOKING ASIAN COUPLE!!! haha i am so so happy for the both of you ;) I can't wait until 138 days from now, so you guys can be a happily married couple! I'll pray for you guys </text>
</MESSAGE>

<MESSAGE>
<identifier>(18 february 2009, 00.18)</identifier>
<author email='kayla.mach@gmail.com'>Kayla Mach</author>
<text>awww.. i'm sooo happy for you guys.  you guys are soo cute!  i love the photos..and your story! :)</text>
</MESSAGE>

<MESSAGE>
<identifier>(17 february 2009, 15.34)</identifier>
<author email='yuhwayang@yahoo.com'>Stephanie yang </author>
<text>WOW~~ this is so cool I think when I get marry I want to get myself one of this webiste!!btw is Mark coming back for sure .....if he is not I can replace him Waaahaa j/k tho.</text>
</MESSAGE>

<MESSAGE>
<identifier>(16 february 2009, 23.24)</identifier>
<author email='liu.isaac@gmail.com'>Isaac</author>
<text>Dood Tuan, the guy in the white shirt is Thomas...</text>
</MESSAGE>

<MESSAGE>
<identifier>(16 february 2009, 19.20)</identifier>
<author email='hayatowong@gmail.com'>Hayato</author>
<text>Gosh! Emily you look gorgeous in those engagement pictures! Isaac you look fantastic too! I am so excited for you guys! Congratulations! Give me a call if you ever need anything 415-302-5260</text>
</MESSAGE>

<MESSAGE>
<identifier>(16 february 2009, 16.36)</identifier>
<author email='chouathao85@hotmail.com'>Choua</author>
<text>I had the hugest grin the whole entire time from reading your blogs, stories, and looking at all your photos. You two were so meant to be together. I am so happy for the both of you. Congratulations!</text>
</MESSAGE>

<MESSAGE>
<identifier>(16 february 2009, 02.07)</identifier>
<author email='Electriceunice@gmail.com'>Eunice</author>
<text>Aaahhhh!!!!! I've been reading your stories and blog entries and it brings me back to the days of our beloved freshman year and visiting Emily and your awesome hall :) who knew this day would come so fast! I'm so excited! Your fatty loves miss you and are SO excited :)</text>
</MESSAGE>

<MESSAGE>
<identifier>(16 february 2009, 00.12)</identifier>
<author email='tuanle8477@gmail.com'>Tuan</author>
<text>Nice website Isaac! I was looking at the picture of you holding Emily backwards from falling while in the dorms and couldn't help but notice someone wearing a white shirt in the background. Looks like Wayne or me. Haha. Miss you guys!</text>
</MESSAGE>

<MESSAGE>
<identifier>(15 february 2009, 23.57)</identifier>
<author email='girlgaucho@gmail.com'>Cathy</author>
<text>This is a really awesome website you've put together.  Congratulations on your life together!</text>
</MESSAGE>

<MESSAGE>
<identifier>(15 february 2009, 23.54)</identifier>
<author email='normanc@live.com'>Norman</author>
<text>Congratulations, Isaac and Emily, I'm glad life is good for the two of you.</text>
</MESSAGE>

<MESSAGE>
<identifier>(15 february 2009, 23.49)</identifier>
<author email='dolphinsuisui@hotmail.com'>Chiaki</author>
<text>Hi Isaac and Emily! Isaac, I just saw your facebook status thing and found out about this website... It's AWESOME!!!! I'm super excited for you two... if there's anything I could do, please let me know! Miss you two!</text>
</MESSAGE>

<MESSAGE>
<identifier>(15 July 2008, 06.06)</identifier>
<author email='liu.isaac@gmail.com'>Isaac</author>
<text>Leave us a message!</text>
</MESSAGE>

</messageboard>
